International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, Aeronautical Industrial District Lodge 91 Records 1984.0017
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series VI: Civil Case 9084-9085: United States Superior Court, District of Connecticut, undated, 1962-1969
  - Subseries H: Attorney's Working Papers, 1944-1968
    - Motion to amend consolidated amended complaint and more definitive statement, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 1208)
    - Motion to strike plaintiff's more definitive statement, 1965-1966 (Box 38, Folder 1209)
    - Trial file, 1960-1967 (Box 38, Folder 1210-1211)
    - Current case notes and correspondence (3355), 1966 (Box 38, Folder 1212)
    - Mrs. Collins Research project: analysis of determinations at Hamilton Standard, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 1213)
    - 9084-9095 witnesses, 1960-1968 (Box 38, Folder 1214)
    - Notes, WMZ: research, 1960-1964 (Box 39, Folder 1215)
    - Working data: finding the facts, 1960-1968 (Box 39, Folder 1216)
    - Working Sheets: finding of facts, party documents, 1960-1965 (Box 39, Folder 1217)
    - Miscellaneous working papers, 1960-1967 (Box 39, Folder 1218)
    - Miscellaneous documents, 1962-1964 (Box 40, Folder 1219)
    - Correspondence and studies, 1965-1967 (Box 41, Folder 1220)
    - Affidavits, 1965-1967 (Box 41, Folder 1221)
    - Discriminatees, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 1222)
    - Proposed list of trial exhibits, 1961-1966 (Box 41, Folder 1223)
    - Dept. 96 study, undated (Box 41, Folder 1224)
    - Summer hires project, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 1225)
    - Seniority are study, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 1226)
    - Miscellaneous support documents and correspondence, 1940s (Box 41, Folder 1227)
    - Miscellaneous documents and correspondence, 1960-1964 (Box 41, Folder 1228)
    - Civil Dockets, U.S. district courts, 1961-1967 (Box 40, Folder 1229)
    - List of 50 workers not reinstated in grounds of strike violence, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 1230)
    - Civil Action, 9084-9085, 1966-1968 (Box 40, Folder 1231)
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1960-1968 (Box 40, Folder 1232-1234)
    - U.S. District Court, NLRB proceedings, 1966 (Box 40, Folder 1235)
    - Pratt and Whitney Foreman's Manual, 1944 (Box 40, Folder 1236)
    - Dictionary of Occupational Titles Vol.I and II, 1949 (Box 40, Folder 1237)
  - Subseries I: Back Pay Data, 1966
    - A - He, 1966 (Box 41, Folder 1238-1453)
    - Hi - So, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 1454-1698)
    - Sp - Z, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 1699-1768)
- Series VII: National Labor Relations Board, undated, 1949-1969
  - Subseries A: Pleadings and Indexes, undated, 1963
    - Charging party's exhibits index, undated (Box 44, Folder 1769)
    - Respondent's exhibits index, undated (Box 44, Folder 1770)
    - General counsel's exhibits index, undated (Box 44, Folder 1771)
    - Pleadings vol. III, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 1772)
  - Subseries B: Briefs and Memoranda, undated, 1963-1969
    - Offer of proof, undated (Box 44, Folder 1773)
    - Second amended answer to complaint, 1963 August 22 (Box 44, Folder 1774)
    - Request of charging party for special permission to appeal, 1963 August 29 (Box 44, Folder 1775)
    - Ruling on appeal, 1964 May 20 (Box 44, Folder 1776)
    - Order consolidating cases, complaint and of hearing, 1964 July (Box 44, Folder 1777)
    - Request of the charging party and the general counsel for special permission to appeal, 1964 August 10 (Box 44, Folder 1778)
    - Opposition to requests of the charging party and the general counsel for special permission to appeal, 1964 August 17 (Box 44, Folder 1779)
    - Motion to amend, 1964 August 18 (Box 44, Folder 1780)
    - Memorandum for the charging party re: statute of limitations in relation to proposed amended complaint, 1964 August 18 (Box 44, Folder 1781)
    - General counsel's offer to proof, 1964 August 28 (Box 44, Folder 1782)
    - Consolidated amended complaint including all amendments made and motions granted by trial examiner up to and including March 19, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 1783)
    - Motion to dismiss the complaint, 1965 April 1 (Box 44, Folder 1784)
    - Ruling on appeal, 1965 June 16 (Box 44, Folder 1785)
    - Respondent's responses to general counsel's proposed findings of material fact; general counsel's motion strike paragraph 11 of respondent's answer and general counsel's motion for summary judgment on paragraph 30 of the complaint, 1965 June 18 (Box 44, Folder 1786)
    - Ruling on appeal, 1965 October 29 (Box 44, Folder 1787)
    - Charging party's opposition to respondent's motion that Board reconsider its ruling on appeal, 1965 November 2 (Box 44, Folder 1788)
    - Respondent's motion that the Board reconsider its ruling on appeal, 1965 November 17 (Box 44, Folder 1787)
    - Motion for trial examiner to take official notice, 1968 June 10 (Box 44, Folder 1788)
    - Memorandum of charging party in support of offer of 301 case evidence, 1968 June 10 (Box 44, Folder 1789)
    - Motion to receive the 301 case evidence, 1968 June 10 (Box 44, Folder 1790)
    - Respondent's brief and reply to "special appeal of counsel", 1968 August 2 (Box 44, Folder 1791)
    - General counsel's brief to trial examiner, vols. 1-2, 1969 January 31 (Box 44, Folder 1792)
    - Brief for charging party, 1969 February 3 (Box 44, Folder 1793)
    - Attorney Ratner statement on "Best case", 1969 July 31 (Box 44, Folder 1794)
    - General counsel's exceptions to the trial examiner's decision, 1969 December 1 (Box 45, Folder 1795)
  - Subseries C: Official Report of the Proceedings, 1964-1967
    - pp. 3387 - 3533, 1964 January 21 (Box 45, Folder 1796)
    - pp. 4332 - 4393, 1964 June 17 (Box 45, Folder 1797)
    - pp. 1 - 18, 1965 February 4 (Box 45, Folder 1798)
    - pp. 19 - 25, 1965 February 4 (Box 45, Folder 1799)
    - pp. 17,974 - 18,187, 1967 August 28 (Box 45, Folder 1800)
    - pp. 18,188 - 18,357, 1967 August 29 (Box 45, Folder 1801)
    - pp. 18,358 - 18,553, 1967 August 30 (Box 45, Folder 1802)
    - pp. 18,554 - 18,689, 1967 August 31 (Box 45, Folder 1803)
    - pp. 18,690 - 18766, 1967 September 1 (Box 45, Folder 1804)
  - Subseries D: Exhibits, undated, 1964
    - Charging Party
      - CP1-CP80 (Box 46, Folder 1805-1814)
      - CP81-CP140 (Box 47, Folder 1815-1820)
      - CP141-CP210 (Box 48, Folder 1821-1827)
      - CP211-CP225 (Box 49, Folder 1828-1830)
      - CP226-CP237 (Box 50, Folder 1831-1839)
      - CP238-CP275 (Box 51, Folder 1840-1850)
    - General Counsel
      - GC1uuu-GC60 (Box 52, Folder 1851-1869)
      - GC61-GC140 (Box 53, Folder 1870-1888)
      - GC141-GC251 (Box 54, Folder 1889-1909)
    - Respondents
      - Unnumbered, Papps testimony, 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1910-1918)
      - R1-R80 (Box 56, Folder 1919-1934)
      - R81-R124 (Box 57, Folder 1935-1967)
      - R125-R168 (Box 58, Folder 1968-2074)
    - Trial Examiner
      - Index (Box 59, Folder 2075)
      - TE1-51 (Box 59, Folder 2076-2098)
    - Oversize Exhibits (Box 59a)
      - CP 261, 262 (2 volumes), 265 (2 volumes)
      - GC 1, 36, 55-59, 68-69, 73, 123, 144 Parts C-D, 147, 223-226
  - Subseries E: Attorney's Working Papers, undated, 1949-1969
    - Special appeal, 1965-1966 (Box 60:, Folder 2099)
    - Appendix to special appeal, 1966 (Box 60:, Folder 2100)
    - Petition to rewrite—Duces Tecum; NLRB memorandum of attorney; Mozart Ratner, prehearing subpoena, 1964 (Box 60:, Folder 2101)
    - Special Appeals to NLRB from rulings of trial examiner, 1963-1964 (Box 60:, Folder 2102)
    - Miscellaneous preparation and research, 1963-1965 (Box 60:, Folder 2103)
    - NLRB charge, 1964-1967 (Box 60:, Folder 2104-2105)
    - Motion to dismiss a complaint and answers thereto, 1965 (Box 60:, Folder 2106)
    - The Machinist, 1961-1963 (Box 61:, Folder 2107)
      - Newsclippings, 1963-1966 (Box 61:, Folder 2108-2109)
      - Contract, 1958 (Box 61:, Folder 2110)
      - Wage reopener, 1949-1950 (Box 61:, Folder 2111)
      - IAM v. United Aircraft settlement negotiations, 1960-1962 (Box 61:, Folder 2112)
    - Responses to newspaper ads re: witnesses, 1963 (Box 61:, Folder 2113)
    - IAM v. UAC overtime records, 1963 (Box 61:, Folder 2114)
    - IAM trial material, 1958-1961 (Box 61:, Folder 2115)
    - Evidence, 1960-1963 (Box 61:, Folder 2116)
    - Steward's manual, 1964 (Box 61:, Folder 2117)
    - Received from Zeman, 1950-1960 (Box 61:, Folder 2118)
    - Motion to strike Paragraph 11 of Respondent's answers, 1963 (Box 61:, Folder 2119)
    - Finding of facts, 1960-1963 (Box 61:, Folder 2120)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950-1952 (Box 61:, Folder 2121)
    - Hamilton Standard post 1960 strike arbitration decisions (Box 61:, Folder 2122)
    - Motion to disqualify trial examiner, 1964 (Box 61:, Folder 2123-2124)
    - Index of transcripts beginning on p. 2691- November 20, 1964 (Box 61:, Folder 2125)
    - Material before and after period of UAC subpoena of 6/5/67, 1967 (Box 61:, Folder 2126)
    - Lodge 1746 Executive Board minutes, 1960 (Box 61:, Folder 2127)
    - Lodge 743 membership meeting minutes, 1960 (Box 61:, Folder 2128)
    - Unity material, 1959-1960 (Box 61:, Folder 2129)
    - Material before and after UAC subpoena of 6/5/67, 1960-1967 (Box 61:, Folder 2130)
    - Original District 91 minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 61:, Folder 2131)
    - WSZ steward witnesses on merit grievances, 1964-1965 (Box 62:, Folder 2132)
    - Exhibits volumes I-IV, 1963-1966 (Box 62:, Folder 2133)
    - IAM and UAW: strike-breaking costs, 1961-1963 (Box 62:, Folder 2134)
    - Condemnation file, 1962-1963 (Box 62:, Folder 2135)
    - NLRB: general counsel's exhibits, 1959-1965 (Box 62:, Folder 2136)
    - NLRB: Exhibit materials, 1960-1963 (Box 62:, Folder 2137)
    - UAW v. IAM District 91: 1746 and 743 arbitration, 1960 (Box 62:, Folder 2138)
    - UAW: Canel operation, 1954-1963 (Box 62:, Folder 2139)
    - Subpoena material, 1967 (Box 62:, Folder 2140)
    - Lodge 1746 minutes, 1967 (Box 62:, Folder 2141)
    - Lodge 1746 minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 2142-2143)
    - Lodge minutes and flyers, 1959-1960 (Box 63, Folder 2144)
    - Correspondence and working papers, 1962-1965 (Box 63, Folder 2145-2147)
    - Letters from Muse to Morse; Seedman to Vandervoort; Tinella to Morse and Nellis to Morse, 1963-1964 (Box 63, Folder 2148)
    - Original complaint in 1-CA-3355, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 2149)
    - NLRB: counter claim in Second Circuit Court, 1963 (Box 63, Folder 2150)
    - Motion for leave to appeal ruling, 1964 (Box 63, Folder 2151)
    - Statement of UAC to NLRB consolidating 5372 with 3355 et al., 1962 (Box 63, Folder 2152)
    - Request of charging party for special appeal; motion to substitute trial examiners and memorandum in support, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 2153)
    - Material turned over to respondent pursuant to subpoena #1350083, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 2154)
    - General counsel's exhibits on contract negotiations between UAC and IAMAW, 1965-1967 (Box 63, Folder 2155)
    - Telegrams re. Negotiations and hearing schedules, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 2156)
    - Reinstatement: Gentile, Edward C., 1969 (Box 63, Folder 2157)
    - Vandervoort digest, undated (Box 63, Folder 2158)
    - Working papers, 1960s (Box 63, Folder 2159)
    - NLRB: hearing notes, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 2160)
- Series VIII: Case No. 133884-133885: Hartford Superior Court, 1960-1969
  - Subseries A: Pleadings, 1963-1969
    - Volume I, 1963-1965 (Box 64)
    - Volume II, 1965-1968
    - Volume III, 1968
    - Volume IV, 1969
  - Subseries B: Briefs and Memoranda, 1963-1969
    - Motion for disclosure, 1964 May 18 (Box 64:, Folder 2161)
    - Memorandum for defendants in opposition to plaintiff's motion to erase, 1963 October 25 (Box 64:, Folder 2162)
    - More specific statement, 1964 November 12 (Box 64:, Folder 2163)
    - Answer to a motion for disclosure, 1965 January 8 (Box 64:, Folder 2164)
    - Docket entries: UAC v. IAM, 1963-1965 (Box 64:, Folder 2165)
    - Defendant's memo, issue of liability, 1968 February 27 (Box 64:, Folder 2166)
    - Plaintiff's brief, 1968 April 4 (Box 64:, Folder 2167)
    - Plaintiff's reply, brief, 1968 May 20 (Box 64:, Folder 2168)
    - Judge Gaffney's decision, 1968 March 31 (Box 64:, Folder 2169)
    - Outline of plaintiff's claims, 1968 July 9 (Box 64:, Folder 2170)
    - Defendant's memorandum, re. Admissibility of evidence, "Strike costs", 1968 July 17 (Box 64:, Folder 2171)
    - Plaintiff's memorandum re. Damages, 1968 September 3 (Box 64:, Folder 2172)
    - Memorandum for defendants, 1968 October 11 (Box 64:, Folder 2173)
    - Brief for defendants, 1968 October 11 (Box 64:, Folder 2174)
    - Plaintiff's reply memorandum, 1968 October 31 (Box 64:, Folder 2175)
    - Judge Gaffney's judgment: memorandum of decision on damages, 1968 November 22 (Box 64:, Folder 2176)
    - Judge Gaffney's decision, 1968 November 26 (Box 64:, Folder 2177)
    - Motion to withdraw appearances, 1969 March 6 (Box 64:, Folder 2178)
    - Request for a finding: rough draft, 1969 April (Box 64:, Folder 2179)
  - Subseries C: Depositions and Witness Testimony, undated, 1965-1968
    - Hayes deposition, 1965 June 16 (Box 64:, Folder 2180)
    - Miscellaneous testimony, 1968 (Box 64:, Folder 2181)
    - Horner testimony, 1968 (Box 64:, Folder 2182)
    - Northrop testimony, pp. 660-799, undated (Box 64:, Folder 2183)
    - Papps testimony, 1969 (Box 64:, Folder 2184)
  - Subseries D: Transcripts, 1964-1968
    - Unnumbered volume, 1964 May 22
    - Volume I, 1968 January 2 - 18
    - Volume II, 1968 January 23 - 25
    - Volume III, 1968 February 27 - 29
    - Volume IV, 1968 March 5 - 7
    - Volume I, 1968 July 2
    - Volume II, 1968 July 3
    - Volume III, 1968 July 9
    - Volume IV, 1968 July 10
    - Volume V, 1968 July 11 (Box 65)
    - Volume VI, 1968 July 12
    - Volume VII, 1968 July 16
    - Volume VIII, 1968 July 17
    - Volume IX, 1968 July 18
    - Volume X, 1968 July 23
    - Volume XI, 1968 July 24 (Box 66)
    - Volume XII, 1968 July 26
  - Subseries E: Exhibits, undated, 1963-1968
    - Defendant's exhibits, 133885, D.E. 1-48, undated (Box 67, Folder 2185-2239)
    - Exhibits C, G, F, K (1 wrapped volume), 1963-1968 (Box 67, Folder 2240)
    - Defendant's exhibits index, undated (Box 67, Folder 2241)
    - Defendant's exhibits 2-6, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 2242-2246)
    - Defendant's exhibits index, undated (Box 67, Folder 2247)
    - Defendant's exhibits, 1-84, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 2248-2319, Box 67)
    - Plaintiff's exhibits, A - Y, [1968] (Box 68:, Folder 2320-2334)
    - Plaintiff's exhibits, AA - ZZ, [1968] (Box 68:, Folder 2335-2359)
    - Plaintiff's exhibits, AAA - ZZZ, [1968] (Box 68:, Folder 2360-2378)
    - Plaintiff's exhibits index, undated (Box 68:, Folder 2379)
    - Plaintiff's exhibits A - Q, [1968] (Box 68:, Folder 2380-2395)
    - Oversize exhibits: C, F, G, K, [1968] (Other 68A)
  - Subseries F: Interrogatory support data, undated
    - 27 B-H (Box 69, Folder 2396-2405)
    - 28 B-H (Box 70, Folder 2406-2417)
    - 29 A-H (Box 70, Folder 2418-2428)
    - 30 A-G (Box 70, Folder 2429-2437)
    - 31 A-G (Box 70, Folder 2438-2440)
    - 39 B-H (Box 70, Folder 2441)
    - 40 B-H (Box 70, Folder 2442-2456)
    - 43 B-H (Box 71, Folder 2457-2470)
    - 44 B-F (Box 71, Folder 2471-2476)
    - 45 B-G (Box 71, Folder 2477-2486)
    - 46 B-G (Box 71, Folder 2487-2501)
    - 47 B-I (Box 72, Folder 2502-2514)
    - 48 (Box 72, Folder 2515)
    - 49 (Box 72, Folder 2516)
  - Subseries G: Attorney's Working Papers, 1960-1968
    - Brief, draft of, 1968 September 20 (Box 73, Folder 2517)
    - Certified copies of complaints in 1960 injunction suits (Box 73, Folder 2518)
    - Documents supplied by plaintiff in response to subpoena, 1960 (Box 73, Folder 2519)
    - Ellis, Joel M.: notes, research and findings, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 2520)
    - Exhibit file, [1968?] (Box 73, Folder 2521)
    - Key job study, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 2522-2523)
    - Subpoena: damages portion, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 2524)
    - Witnesses, 1968 (Box 73, Folder 2525-2526)
- Series IX: Other Legal Cases, 1960-1969
  - Subseries A: United States Supreme Court, 1964
    - Case no. 533, 1964 October (Box 74, Folder 2527)
    - Case no. 749, 1964 October (Box 74, Folder 2528)
  - Subseries B: United States District Court: District of Connecticut, 1960-1967
    - Civil case no. 8380, 1960 June 16 (Box 74, Folder 2529)
    - Civil case no. 8586, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 2530)
    - Civil case no 11,466: Hoban v. United Aircraft Corp.
      - Pleadings, 1966 June - August (Box 74, Folder 2531)
      - Hearing: recognition, 1966 June (Box 74, Folder 2532-2535)
      - Respondents memorandum of points and authorities in opposition to board's petition for injunction, 1966 June 23 (Box 74, Folder 2536)
      - Memorandum...in response to respondent's motion to amend findings of fact and conclusions of law and to enter a new judgment, 1966 September 14 (Box 74, Folder 2537)
      - Ruling of defendant's motion to amend finding of fact and conclusions of law and to enter a new judgment, 1966 September 29 (Box 74, Folder 2538)
      - Order dissolving temporary injunction, 1966 September 29 (Box 74, Folder 2539)
      - Motion to vacate order dissolving temporary injunction, 1967 February 14 (Box 74, Folder 2540)
      - Proposed finding of fact and conclusions of law, 1967 April 21 (Box 74, Folder 2541)
      - Proposed order granting motion to vacate order dissolving temporary injunction, 1967 April 21 (Box 74, Folder 2542)
      - Further brief in support of motion to vacate order dissolving temporary injunction, 1967 April 21 (Box 74, Folder 2543)
      - Respondent's post hearing brief opposing petitioner's motion that the Court vacate order dissolving temporary injunction and expand temporary injunction, 1967 May 5 (Box 74, Folder 2544)
      - Brief for Lodges 1746 and 743...amicus curiae, 1967 May 10 (Box 74, Folder 2545)
      - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 2546)
      - Attorney's working papers, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 2547)
      - Exhibit indexes, undated (Box 74, Folder 2548)
      - Court exhibits, [1966?] (Box 74, Folder 2549)
      - Defendant's exhibits 101-112, [1966?] (Box 74, Folder 2550-2561)
      - Respondent's exhibits A - F, [1966?] (Box 74, Folder 2562)
      - Government exhibits 1-54, [1966?] (Box 75, Folder 2563-2608)
      - Plaintiff's exhibits 100-161, [1966?] (Box 75, Folder 2609-2667)
    - Civil case no. 10,324, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 2668)
    - Civil case no. 10, 535, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 2669)
  - Subseries C: United States Court of Appeals: Second Circuit, 1963-1964
    - Case no. 28,490, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 2670)
    - Case no. 28, 595, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 2671)
    - Case no 28, 904, 1963-1964 (Box 77, Folder 2672)
  - Subseries D: United States Court of Appeals: District of Columbia, 1966-1968
    - Case nos. 21,469 and 21, 690, 1966-1968 (Box 77, Folder 2673)
  - Subseries E: Hartford Superior Court, 1960
    - Case nos. 121663 and 121664, 1960 (Box 77, Folder 2674-2675)
  - Subseries F: National Labor Relations Board, 1960-1969
    - 1-CA-3351, 1960-1961 (Box 77, Folder 2676)
    - 1-CA-3357 and 1-CA-3358, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 2677)
    - 1-CA-4003, 1965 (Box 77, Folder 2678)
    - 1-CA-4201 and 1-CA-4202, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 2679)
    - 1-CA-4361 and 1-CA-4477, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 2680)
    - 1-CA-4491 and 1-CA-4492, 1963-1964 (Box 77, Folder 2681)
    - 1-CA-4587 and 1-CA-4588, 1964 (Box 77, Folder 2682)
    - 1-CA-5030, 1965-1966 (Box 77, Folder 2683)
    - 1-CA-5245 and 1-CA-5372, 1966 (Box 77, Folder 2684-2686)
    - 1-CA-5710 et al., 1966-1968 (Box 78, Folder 2687-2691)
    - 1-CA-5721 and 1-CA-5722, 1966-1967 (Box 78, Folder 2692)
    - 1-CA-5786, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 2693)
    - 1-CA-6198, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 2694)
    - 1-CA-6229 to 6232, 1967-1969 (Box 78, Folder 2695)
    - 1-CA-6475 and 1-CA-6602, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 2696)
    - 1-CA-6545, 1968-1969 (Box 78, Folder 2697)
    - 1-CB-1429, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 2698)
    - 1-CB-1474, 1968-1969 (Box 78, Folder 2699)
    - 12-CB-967, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 2700)
    - 1-UC-37, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 2701)
  - Subseries G: Attorney's Working Papers, undated, 1961-1964
    - Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 79, Folder 2702)
    - Ratner, Mozart: correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 2703)
    - Burke - Gwinn: questions, undated (Box 79, Folder 2704)
    - Charges for Canel and Southington, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 2705)
    - Records research project: unidentified case, undated (Box 79, Folder 2706)
    - Notes, undated (Box 79, Folder 2707)
- Series X: Conference Material, undated, 1960-1979
  - Subseries A: General Files, undated, 1962-1979
    - AFL-CIO Union Industrial Engineering Institutes, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 2708)
    - Education, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 2709)
    - IAMAW
      - Firms in the brewery industry, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 2710)
      - Grand Lodge and Special Representatives Inst., 1966 (Box 80, Folder 2711)
      - Machinists Leadership Schools, 1969, 1979 (Box 80, Folder 2712)
      - Machinists Non-Partisan Political League: Staff Institute, 1966 May 22-27 (Box 80, Folder 2713)
      - Mailing lists, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 2714)
      - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 2715)
      - Model Agreement, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 2716)
      - Strike Policies, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 2717)
    - Understanding Time Study, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 2718)
    - Union label, undated (Box 80, Folder 2719)
    - University of Connecticut, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 2720)
    - Pennsylvania State University, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 2721)
  - Subseries B: IAMAW Aerospace Conference, 1966-1977
    - 13th, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 2722)
    - 14th, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 2723)
    - 15th, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 2724-2725)
    - 16th, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 2726)
    - 17th, 1970 (Box 80, Folder 2727)
    - 18th, 1971 (Box 80, Folder 2728-2729)
    - 25th (Cassette tape), 1977 (Box 80, Folder 2730)
  - Subseries C: Connecticut State Council of Machinists, 1970-1972
    - Training Seminar, 1970 January (Box 81, Folder 2731)
    - Semi-annual conference material
      - 1970 January (Box 81, Folder 2732)
      - 1970 June (Box 81, Folder 2733)
      - 1971 Janaury (Box 81, Folder 2734)
      - 1971 June (Box 81, Folder 2725)
      - 1972 January (Box 81, Folder 2726)
  - Subseries D: Other Conferences, 1967-1971
    - Connecticut Education Conference, 1969, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 2727-2728)
    - Connecticut Governors Conference on Human Rights, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 2729)
    - Connecticut State Labor Council, AFL-CIO, Convention
      - 1969 (Box 82, Folder 2730)
      - 1970 (Box 82, Folder 2731)
      - 1971 (Box 82, Folder 2732)
    - COPE Area Conference, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 2733)
    - IAMAW
      - Atomic Energy Lodges of IAM Conference, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 2734)
      - National Electronics and New Technology Conference, 1969 (Box 82, Folder 2735)
      - Staff Conference, 1969-1971 (Box 82, Folder 2736-2738)
    - New England Conference of Machinists, 1970 (Box 82, Folder 2739)
- Series XI: Printed Material, 1937-1983
  - Subseries A: Newsclippings, undated, 1965-1982
    - Scrapbooks, undated; (4 volumes) (Box 82A)
    - undated (Box 83, Folder 2740)
    - 1965-1966 (Box 83, Folder 2741-2743)
    - 1967 (Box 83, Folder 2744-2746)
    - 1968 (Box 83, Folder 2747-2750)
    - 1969 (Box 83, Folder 2751-2752)
    - 1970 (Box 84, Folder 2753-2755)
    - Connecticut politics, 1970 (Box 84, Folder 2756-2765)
    - 1971 (Box 85, Folder 2766-2776)
    - 1973-1974 (Box 85:, Folder 2777)
    - 1976-1978 (Box 85:, Folder 2778-2780)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 85:, Folder 2781-2783)
  - Subseries B: Flyers, undated, 1953-1982
    - District 91, undated (Box 86)
      - undated (Box 86:, Folder 2784)
      - 1968-1969 (Box 86:, Folder 2785-2786)
      - 1970 (Box 86:, Folder 2787-2789)
      - 1971 (Box 86:, Folder 2790-2798)
      - 1972-1982 (Box 86:, Folder 2799-2807)
    - Lodges
      - 1946 (Box 86:, Folder 2808)